tweetizen.com 2013-04-10

# About Tweetizen

This policy tells you how we use and protect your personal information on http://www.tweetizen.com. This policy is effective as of March 1, 2009. 

## Information We Collect

**No Information Required:** There may be limited parts of our site that you may use without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.

**Information We Collect Upon Registration:** In order to use certain parts of our site we require that you provide us with some basic personal information such as your Twitter user name, and Twitter password. We need your Twitter username and password because Twitter requires that we authenticate your Twitter credentials in order to send & receive information to Twitter on your behalf.

**Information We Collect From Twitter:** If you give us your Twitter username and password, we can and do access the information in your Twitter account as allowed according to the Twitter API. We do this in order to provide functionality for the Tweetizen service. This information may include Twitter messages you have sent, Twitter messages posted by people you're following, your direct messages, and public profile information.

**Optional Information:** You may have the opportunity to provide us with additional, optional information about yourself. You may choose to do this because it enhances the Tweetizen experience for you and/or other Tweetizen users.

**Log Data:** We may record some or all of the information your browser sends to our servers. This may include information such as your IP address, the domain you are visiting from, your browser type, the pages you visit on our site, and terms you may have searched for. We use this information to monitor and improve the technical performance of our site and to improve the overall Tweetizen service.

## How We Use Your Information

Our primary purpose in collecting and using your personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience.

**Interacting with Twitter:** As noted above, we use your Twitter username and password to send information to and receive information from Twitter on your behalf.

**Communication:** If you provide us your personal contact information on Tweetizen (e.g., email, phone number) we may use it to provide you Tweetizen functionality, market to you, and/or provide you information about the Tweetizen service. If you do not wish to receive such communication or information from us, please unsubscribe using the instructions provided in the communication. We may also send messages to your Twitter or Tweetizen account just like any other user of the Twitter or Tweetizen services.

**Improving our Service:** We may use personal information to better understand user behavior, and research & analysis in order to operate and improve the Tweetizen service.

**Aggregated Non-Personal Information:** We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties.

**We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent.**

## How We Protect Your Information

We understand that you are trusting us with the personal information you share with us. We take this very seriously and treat your information as an asset that must be protected. Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We use tools (encryption, passwords, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, despite our best efforts, there may be third parties that try to hack into our systems or intercept our data communications. Therefore, although we will work very hard to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee that that your personal information or private communications will remain private 100% of the time.

## Cookies

In order to improve the Tweetizen service and your experience, we use "cookie" technology. A cookie is a small file placed on your hard drive that can be used to do things such as: help us better understand how people use our service, remember your settings when you when you repeatedly visit our site, and let you customize your Tweetizen experience. A few additional things you might want to know about cookies:

  * You can adjust your cookie settings in your browser (and may turn off cookies entirely)
  * There are certain features that are only available through the use of cookies
  * We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information

## Our Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, or protect anyone's rights, property or safety. If we do disclose your information for one of these reasons, we will do it in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your personal information with:

  * Third party service providers necessary to provide the service (e.g., data hosting providers), in which case we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and take appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * Other third parties whom you explicitly ask us to send your information to
  * Law enforcement or other government officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such event, we will disclose information that is relevant to the investigation.
